[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "бить",
    "options": [
      "杀死",
      "忘记",
      "敲打",
      "压下"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "пробивать — пробить",
    "options": [
      "打碎",
      "打通",
      "杀死",
      "迷路"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "прибивать — прибить",
    "options": [
      "打通",
      "打人",
      "打碎",
      "钉上"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "забивать — забить",
    "options": [
      "打通",
      "忘记",
      "射进球",
      "迷路"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "выбиваться — выбиться",
    "options": [
      "打碎",
      "忘记",
      "杀死",
      "挣脱"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "набивать — набить",
    "options": [
      "钉上",
      "塞满",
      "打碎",
      "忘记"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "отбирать — отбить",
    "options": [
      "忘记",
      "打碎",
      "夺回",
      "钉上"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "отбиваться — отбиться",
    "options": [
      "打碎",
      "抵抗",
      "忘记",
      "钉上"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "разбивать — разбить",
    "options": [
      "射进球",
      "忘记",
      "打碎",
      "杀死"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "сбиваться — сбиться",
    "options": [
      "迷路",
      "忘记",
      "钉上",
      "打人"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "убивать — убить",
    "options": [
      "迷路",
      "忘记",
      "打通",
      "杀死"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "explanation": ""
  }
]
